汤姆 高兴你能到来
Tom, glad to see you made it.
我才不会错过
I wouldn't miss it.
国家气候学会 太空总署指挥
National Weather Institute, this is NASA Command.
转移牧场一号人造卫星控制
Transferring control of satellite Gulf-001...
六秒后
... in six...
五 四
... five... four...
输入来源密码
Do source code.
禁止使用 需用核准密码
输入现时使用密码
Enter current access code. Captains Trilling, Gilder...
转移完成
控制了 是我们的了
We got it. It's ours.
请注意
Be advised...
接收到牧场一号卫星 谢谢
...we have received satellite Gulf-001. Thank you, Houston.
好了 且看它们有何本领
All right, let's see what she can do.
启动观察功能
Activating observation function.
准备第二阶段
Setting for Stage 2.
这是什么?
What have we got here?
删除掉
Clean it up.
她转身了
Oh, my God, she's turning over!
增大整幅图像
Apply full-image enhancing.
好砘
Holy guacamole!
这东西有效
The damn thing works.
那该死的邓查维
That goddamn Travis Dane.
视像这么清晰目标系统定很好
If the optical circuits are this good, the targeting system must be great.
丹会喜欢的
Dane would love this.
太空总暑以为这是气象卫星
NASA thinks this is a weather satellite.
进行武器检查
Let's do a weapons check.
这不是国会认为的浪费金钱
This wasn't the bust Congress thought it was.
国会不知道的事对我们没伤害
What Congress doesn't know won't hurt them, or us.
有不妥吗?
Something wrong, Captain?
可惜丹今天不在这里
It's too bad Dane wasn't here today.
屈维斯丹是个疯子
Travis Dane was a nut.
他把车驶进湖里
He drove his car into a lake.
他是疯的
He was crazy.
找到尸体没有?
They find the body yet?
没有 只找到车
No, just the car.
及写有『有志者事竟成』字条
And a note that said: "Chance favors the prepared mind."
奇怪吧?
Odd, huh?
丹也是怪的
But then, so was Dane.
你们做得好
Captains, you did a hell of a job.
该引以为傲
Be proud of yourselves.
周末愉快
Enjoy your weekend.
谢谢 将军
Thank you, General.
我可和你谈吗?失陪
Can I talk to you? Excuse me.
周末愉快
Have a nice weekend.
回家去
Go home.
周末空军学院有航空展
There's an air show at the Air Force Academy this weekend.
要和我去吗?
Maybe you'd like to join me for a drink?
研究新的技技
Check out the new technologies.
高层军官会出席 很难说
All the top brass will be there. Who knows...
会对你的事业有助
...it might help your career.
抱歉 我有节目
Sorry, I have plans.
好的 我明白
Yeah, sure, I understand.
一如将军所说
Like the General said...
你做得好
...you did a good job.
过奖
Thank you...
长官
...sir.
快点 你迟到了
Let's go, you're running late.
你去了哪儿?
Where have you been?
有特别任务?
On a special op?
很荣幸
Lieutenant, always a pleasure.
我知道 你不能对我说
I know, you can't tell me.
很抱歉关于你哥哥的事
Sorry to hear about your brother.
我也很难过
Me, too.
得赶上火车 它45分钟后开行
We must hurry to make that train. It leaves in 45 minutes.
你们为何坐火车到加州
Why are you two taking a train to California?
她的父母因飞机失事去世
Would you fly if your parents died in a plane crash?
凯西
Hi, Casey.
这儿比你主持时好多了 我能搞定 可是
This place runs better when you're here. I can run it, but...
你不懂烹饪
You can't cook.
顾客为你而非为我才来光顾
The patrons come here for you, Casey, not for me.
可爱的孩子
She's a cute kid.
这是你的侄女?   是的 是我唯一亲人
- Is that your niece? - Yes. She's the only family I have left.
我不知是否认得她
I don't know if I'll recognize her.
快点 否则错过了火车
Come on, we'll miss that train.
我错过兄长的葬礼 所以
I missed my brother's funeral, so...
我们不会错过火车
...we won't miss the train.
请注意
Your attention, please.
由丹佛往麻省列车现在登车
The Grand Continental Service from Denver to Los Angeles, now boarding.
莎拉雷贝克有拿车票吗?
Has a Sarah Ryback picked up any tickets?
凯西叔叔
Uncle Casey.
很高兴看见你
Nice to see you, too.
你亭亭玉立了
You've gotten big.
五年的变化会很大
A lot can happen in five years.
等一等
Just a moment.
最近在忙些什么?
So, what have you been doing?
处理飞机失事 葬礼等事
Taking care of airplane crashes, funerals, stuff like that.
是的 那么
Yeah, so...
行了 三号月台
Here you are. Track 3.
我刚才在想
You know, I was thinking...
你以前收集玩具熊我给你买了
I remembered that you collect teddy bears and I got you one.
它不及你部份的藏品
It isn't as good as some of yours...
你亦可能太成熟
...and I know you may be too mature...
不会再玩玩具熊了
...to hang out with teddy bears now.
但主要的是心意
It's the thought that counts.
谢谢
Thanks.
这方面我倒没有受训
I guess I'm not trained for this.
请问
Excuse me.
我可替你拿行李吗?不错的
Can I carry your bags? Oh, nice...
奖章
...medal you got there.
是海军十字动章
It's a Navy Cross.
我叔叔是海军但他没你帅
My uncle was in the Navy, but he didn't look like you.
这是什么?
- What is that? - This?
喷雾防身器
It's Mace.
我要假装忙着让我替你拿行李吧
All right. Listen, I have to look busy, so why don't you let me take your bag?
否则我会给辞退
If I don't, I could get fired.
这样我便没钱念大学 我会穷
If I get fired, I won't have enough money for college, and I'll be poor.
这样可以了 我喜欢
This will work. I like this.
你说你在哪一个车厢?
What compartment did you say you were in?
我的车厢
My compartment.
吉尔上尉
Captain Gilder...
很高兴看见你
...fancy meeting you here.
顺林上尉 喝香槟吧
Have some champagne, Captain Trilling.
等候的人会有好东西
Good things come to those who wait.
你已等得够久了
Okay, you waited.
不知那边的女孩子喝些什么
I was wondering what that girl over there is drinking.
那个喝莱姆汽水的女孩吗?
The little girl with the tonic and lime and the bad ID?
正是那一个
That's the one.
你不喝酒?
- You're not drinking? - No.
和我一起喝 我不喜欢独个儿喝
Join me. I don't like drinking alone.
你的饮料没有酒
There's no alcohol in that.
反正你什么也知道
Yeah, you always knew everything, anyway.
我们可以聊点轻松点的吗?
Do you think we could have a pleasant conversation?
可以
Sure.
谈谈你和我爸为何不讲话吧
Let's talk about why you and my dad stopped talking.
听着
Listen...
我知道你父亲和我意见不合
...I know that your father and I had our differences...
但我爱他
...but that doesn't mean I didn't love him.
你没不和他说话
But you didn't even talk.
那是很久以前
Time goes by...
时光飞逝 不知不觉间
...it seems to fly, and before you know it...
事情发生了
...things happen.
但我从没想过
But I never thought...
我会没机会把事情说清楚
...I'd never get a chance to straighten things out with him.
你知道
You know...
他在并不是好惹的人
...he didn't get the medals in the service by being a choirboy.
别这样子说我爸爸
I don't want you talking about my father that way.
我要喝酒
I need a drink.
有什么是最烈的?
What's the strongest stuff you got?
波多黎各甜酒如何?
How about Puerto Rican Rum?
凯西叔叔
Uncle Casey...
我不想争吵
I don't want to fight.
我到这儿前答应自己要把感受说
I just promised myself before I got here, that I would tell you how I felt.
现在
Now...
我们做朋友吧
...let's just be friends.
好的
Okay.
我到处走走
I'm going for a walk.
里面是什么?
- What's up? - What's in there?
是高度机密 我不能让你进去
It's top secret. I can't let you get in there.
里面是些什么?
What's in there?
别迫我出手制止你 我有练举重
Don't make me restrain you, because I've been working out, see?
我轻易制服你
It'd be easy to do that.
好的 制服我吧
Okay. Restrain me.
你要我这样?
You want me to?
是的
Yeah.
好吧 这很容易
All right, if you say so. It'll be real easy.
里面有拖把
There's a mop...
扫扫以及许多发臭的东西
...a broom and a lot of smelly stuff you want to avoid.
谁教你的?
Who taught you that?
我十一岁时叔叔教我自卫技
When I was 11 years old, my uncle taught me all this neat stuff.
和你一起的那个人?
That's the dude that's with you?
是的
Yeah...
我猜是的
...I guess.
我亦可以
I can do that.
你在写什么?
What are you writing?
是本书 我的回忆录
It's a book. My memoirs, stuff like that.
你这么年轻便写回忆录?
Aren't you too young to be writing your memoirs?
我知不合规矩但给我喝杯酒吧
I know it's against the rules, but give me a shot of something.
你可否把它们放上去?
Can you put those up there?
可以
Yeah.
你的李小龙侄女怎么回事了?
What's up with that niece of yours, Miss Bruce Lee?
她差点杀了我
She almost killed me.
上!
Up!
是你教她的?
You taught her all that shit?
只教了她一点点
I taught her a few things.
还好她是女孩子
She's lucky she's a girl.
我也懂功夫的
I know some of that stuff myself.
我听说了
That's what I hear.
是我听你说的
Usually from you, but that's what I hear.
别给他白兰地 我要用来做蛋糕
Don't give him the brandy. I need it for the cake.
看看
Look at that.
因为火车摇动我的手法欠流畅
Because the train is rocking, it's cramping my style.
我做给莎拉吃的 她最爱吃的
I'm making this for Sarah because it's her favorite thing.
高温烘十五分钟
Fifteen minutes, on high.
其余的听天由命
The rest is up to God.
去找莎拉吧 给她一个惊喜
Now, go find Sarah, and we'll surprise her.
是什么声音?
What was that?
那称为
It's called a...
高潮
...orgasm.
似是雷管 列车一定是在无讯号
Sounds like torpedoes. We must be in dark territory.
是什么回事?
What the hell is this?
他们不是铁路局的人
They're not our guys.
有什么事?
What's the trouble?
是什么回事?
What's going on?
有人中枪
Someone's been shot.
在哪儿?
Where?
就在这儿
Here.
火车受控了
Loco secured.
快!你们有四分钟
Move! You have four minutes.
大家到火车后面去 别要我再说
Everybody to the back of the train! Don't make me ask twice!
各人上去!快点!
Everybody up those stairs! Move it! Come on!
要那婊子住口否则杀了她
Shut that bitch up or I will! Let's move it!
上楼梯!
Get up the stairs!
这是什么?还有什么?走吧!
What the fuck is this? Anything else? Go! Get out of here!
打开行李舱门!
Open the door to the baggage car!
搜查行李
Check the baggage.
搜过了
Baggage checked.
还有英雄吗?
Any other heroes?
餐车有一人死了
Trouble in the dining car. One casualty.
找掩护!
Take cover!
四名厨师 查过了
Four cooks. Check.
知道 继续驱赶乘客
Copy that. Continue with the cleanup.
二十秒后离去
We leave in 20 seconds.
这方面我训练有素
This, I'm trained for.
天啊
Oh, my God.
你们在这儿
Well, here you are.
料不到在这儿找到你们
The last place anyone would expect to find you.
不可思议
Amazing.
穿衣服
Put something on.
请坐 上尉们
Have a seat, Captains.
他们说你死了
They said you were dead.
是的 很安详
Yeah, very restful.
没有电话
No phone calls.
你们可真顽皮
You two have been very naughty.
单位命令禁止雇员发生关系
ATAC has strict rules against employees getting involved with each other.
你是为此而来的吗?
Is that what this is about?
是的 我装死以方便去劫载客火
Yeah, right. I faked my own death and hijacked a passenger train...
因为我关心你和谁上床
...because I care about who you're fucking.
不 我想知你会违反那一条规例
No, I wondered what other rules you'd be willing to break.
准备传送
On-line transmission's ready, sir.
别走开
Don't go away.
各位晚安 我是你们的挪掠者
Good evening, everyone. This is your captor speaking.
你们今晚的行程有些许改变
There's been a slight change in your travel plans tonight.
请你们移到火车最后两节车厢
You have, you will note, been moved to the last two cars of the train...
是为了你们的安全
... for your own well-being.
首先请注意受高度训练的人员
First, I'd like to call your attention to the highly trained men...
他们手持自动武器
... with the automatic weapons in your cars.
在紧急情况下他们会奉命杀你们
In the event of an emergency, they may be called upon to shoot you.
我们关心你们的安全
Your safety is our primary concern.
可是 若你们轻举妄动
However, if you try anything stupid...
依据联邦法我会杀了你们
... federal regulations require that I kill you.
他疯了
He's insane.
所以求求你们
So, please...
别程英雄
... no hero shit.
给我密码
Your access code, please.
我永不会
I'll never...
告诉你密码的
...give you the code.
你的心说你会的
The psychological profile we have on you says you will.
若想证明档案是错的
However, if you wish to prove the profile incorrect...
那就别动看看当那炙热的铁针
...sit back and see what happens when an intensely hot needle...
刺进这明目时会变得怎样
...penetrates the lens of one of the most beautiful eyes on earth.
铁针可轻易刺过水晶体
The needle point will pass through the lens with very little difficulty.
热力会烧灼及封合伤口
The heat will cauterize and seal the wound.
但铁针仍继续把热力
But the instrument will continue to transfer heat...
传至眼内的液体
...to the fluid in the eyeball.
液体沸腾而
The fluid comes to a boil and...
眼球
...the eyeball itself...
爆炸
...explodes.
J B N
J-B-N-1...
1 2 1
他无法使用的
He can't use it.
你认为他何以这样做?
Why do you think he's doing this?
因为他是疯的
Because he's crazy.
你们可稍后再争论 下一个!
You can argue that point later. Next!
我们准备好没有?
Are we up for this?
你无法进入系统 它有四重防御
You can't hack into the system. There are quadruple blocks.
即使可进入各密码亦要同时输入
Even if he could, the codes need to be entered simultaneously.
这儿能量不够你见过单位发电机
There's not enough power here. You've seen the ATAC generators.
这是不可能的!
Oh, for Christ's sake, it's impossible!
你是知道的
You know that!
密码是不同的!你不能再用它们
The codes are different! You can't use them anymore!
没用的!他无法使用!
It's no good! He can't use them!
快告诉他密码!给他密码!
For God's sake, please, give him the code! Give him the code!
E U I
E-U-I...
4 7 6
...4- 7-6.
我不单发明了牧场一号还把它增
I not only invented Grazer, I've updated it...
使用单位所不知的电子磁场光普
...to use part of the electromagnetic spectrum ATAC is only dimly aware of.
那是什么?
What is that?
只要我们在动讯号是完全透明的
As long as we're moving, the signal is completely transparent.
你亦知道
As you can see...
我们在火车上六小时内不会停车
...we're on a choo-choo. No stop signs for six hours.
单位会很想掌握这种技技
ATAC would kill to get a hold of this technology.
事实上
In fact...
我相信他们想得到
...I'm sure they'll try.
这技技在地底 水底均发挥
Works just as well underground, underwater.
我不单设计系统
I not only designed the system...
亦设计了防御
...I designed the blocks.
执行超驰
你做什么?
What're you doing, Dane?
我在连接单位系统
I'm hacking into ATAC, Linda.
现在
Now...
看着
...watch...
这个
...this.
禁止使用 输入使用密码
转移完成
再由我掌握了
It's mine again.
住口!
Shut the fuck up!
我们瞄准了
We're locked.
他们还没走
Oh, they're still here.
我不再需要他们 他们可以走
I don't need them anymore. They can go now.
快点
Move it, asshole!
来吧
Come on, gorgeous.
难道你不知那人是疯的?
Don't you know that man's crazy? Do you realize what he could do?
他付给我许多钱
He's paying me a lot of money.
原来如此
That's why you're doing this?
可恶
Goddamn it.
三十万页密码 或是
Three-hundred thousand pages of code...
60分钟的色情互动
...or 60 minutes of triple-X interactive...
性变态虐待淫衣物
...rubber-and-leather-bondage porno.
技技可用以美化
Technology can be used for beauty...
或是降格
...or debasement.
直至你接驳上
And until you plug it in...
是难以知道的
...you just can't tell.
遥控使用能力
天啊
我带了目标瞄准密码
I seem to have brought the targeting codes.
我要稳当关上耙簧让偶按
I want every window and door locked and secured. Airtight.
火车受控制
The train is secure.
十分钟完成主要安装电话两分钟
The major installation is T minus ten. The phone lines are two.
我们搜查火车找游勇
We're sweeping the train for stragglers. Excuse me.
好了 各位
Okay, people...
开始派对吧
...let's start this party.
轨迹转移
关闭牧场一号卫星
什么回事?
What's going on?
上尉 给我报告
Captain, give me a report.
我仍在追查
I'm still searching.
试这个
Try this.
这是什么?   它消失了 先生
- What is it? - It's gone, sir.
什么消失了?  牧场一号卫星
- What's gone? - Grazer One.
什么意思?它还显示在屏幕上
What do you mean, it's gone? Bring it up on the screen.
好像有人拿走了
It's like someone took it.
怎可能有人拿走?
How could someone take it?
没人知道它在上空
Nobody knows it's there.
找它的下落 它设计成没法追测的
- Find the damn thing. - We designed it to be undetectable.
但我们可以
But not from us, for Christ's sake!
我要全面检查系统 两分钟后要
I want a full systems-check in two minutes.
已进入二号密码
We're in Code 2 status.
立即找吉儿 顺林和贝克来
Gilder, Trilling and Tom Breaker, ASAP.
快一点
All right, let's move it!
彭先生 他们无法进入系统
Mr. Penn, ATAC is now locked out of their own system.
牧场一号卫星全由我控制
Grazer One is fully under my control.
我以为你是持枪的那班人
I thought you were one of those ugly men with guns.
你做什么?
What are you doing?
天气适宜到外面走走 这是什么
It was just a nice day for a stroll. What's in here?
行李室 别进去 他们向我开枪
It's the baggage car, but don't go in. They shot at me in there.
你做什么?
What are you doing?
想送命吗?
Trying to get killed?
他们有枪
There are guys with guns out there.
过来
Come here.
我不会过来 别要我大叫 过来
- I ain't coming out there. - Don't make me yell. Come here.
接通了投资者?
Investors on the line?
来自亚洲及中东的客户
Clients from Asia and the Middle East are standing by, sir.
各位?
Gentlemen.
今天好吗?天气如何?
How are we today? How's the weather out there? Sunny and sandy?
现在是示范时间
Now, look, it's demonstration time.
你们有人不相信
Some of you have trouble with the idea of...
非原发性地区的地震活动
...a non-terrestrially originated seismic event.
但我想你们紧密注意中国
But I want you to watch China very closely for the next ten minutes.
有什么问题 系统不让我们使用
- What's the problem? - The system won't let us in.
什么意思?我们就是系统
The system? What do you mean? We are the system.
吉儿和顺林有消息吗? 仍在找他们
- Any word from Gilder and Trilling? - We're still looking.
亦不见了他们?
You lose them, too?
广州肥料场会粪便四践
This is where the shit will really start to fly. A fertilizer plant in Guangzhou.
肥料场?
A fertilizer plant?
我把粪便弄的四处皆是震惊世界
Yeah, I'm going to shock the world by spreading ca-ca all over the place.
广州的肥料场其实是化武工场
Guangzhou is a chemical weapons plant posing as a fertilizer plant.
我们知道 中国亦知我们知道
We know this. The Chinese know we know.
我们假装不知中国假装我们不知
But we pretend we don't, and the Chinese pretend they believe we don't know...
但他们知道
...but they know.
人人均知道
Everybody knows.
我去把火车刹停 逃之大吉
I'm gonna pull the brake cord, stop the train and get the hell out of here.
我会死的 我是侍者
I'm going to die. I'm a fucking porter.
你是个厨师
You're a fucking cook.
你在这件事上要相信我
You gotta trust me on this one, okay?
这儿有电话或通讯器吗?
Is there a phone or com unit here?
火车有无线电楼下酒廊有电话
There's a radio in the locomotive and a pay phone downstairs in the lounge.
我会设法通知当局
I'll try to call the cavalry.
你搜查行李是否有武器
Meanwhile, search the bags for a weapon or something that can be used as one.
我碰行李便会给辞退
If I even touch a bag, I lose my job.
我更关心
I'm more concerned...
给胁持作人质的乘客生命
...about the lives of these people being held as hostages.
人质
The hostages.
我不想他们受伤害
I don't want them hurt.
请你留心 彭先生
Now, pay close attention, Mr. Penn.
我会把大灾难弄成似是小事一桩
I'm about to make the Bhopal disaster look like a Girl Scout picnic.
在那儿 回来了
There. It's back.
没什么的 是轻微出错 虚惊一场
You see, it's nothing. A minor glitch. False alarm.
那是什么东西?
What the hell is that?
毒气 化学火灾
Poison gas, chemical fire...
方圆一百里内完全毁灭
...total devastation for a 100-mile radius.
以千计的人会死去
Thousands of people are going to die.
你听着和依我吩咐做
Just listen and do what I say.
掩护和隐藏
Cover and concealment...
你跟别人同样知道
...you know as much as anybody!
脱下白色的外衣 是的
Right.
你再碰我便会有麻烦
You touch me again, it's your ass.
目标密码
Targeting codes.
他们开始我们的次序
- They've started our targeting sequence. - It's arming.
太荒妙 定是操作错误
This is nuts. There must be some kind of malfunction.
它在别处受到控制
It's being controlled elsewhere.
目标是中国
Oh, Jesus, the target's mainland China.
不会吧!
Not China!
不能瞄准核子国家
Not somebody nuclear.
是什么回事?
What's going on?
天啊
Sweet Jesus!
它进入进取模式
She's into acquisition mode.
把它关掉吧!
Somebody shut it down!
他们辞退我
They fired me.
夺去一切
Took everything.
它准备命中东西
She's powering up for a hit.
说这技技不需要
Said the technology wasn't essential.
炸了它!
Blow it!
关掉它!
Shut it down!
没反应
No response.
他们要的 定会得到
They wanted it! They'll get it!
执行
有志者事竟成
彭以前这样说
That's what Dane used to say.
通知五角大厦的贝兹上将
Call Admiral Bates at the Pentagon.
他在科罗拉多出席航空展
Admiral Bates is here in Colorado attending an air show.
那立即要他前来
Then get him here, now.
各位 你们看见它是有效的
Gentlemen, as you can see, it works.
这是只此一次的机会
This is a one-time offer.
五角大厦二百尺下的小裂缝
Two hundred feet below the Pentagon, is an itty-bitty crack...
我提议把它加大加阔
...which I propose to make great, big and wide.
在它上面的是核子反应器
Directly above it is a strike-hard nuclear reactor.
但它承受不了攻击
It ain't hard enough.
我们消灭五角大厦
We'll take out the Pentagon...
神
...and God...
真主
...Allah...
若风向对的话
...and the wind's willing...
会遍及华府及东岸大部份地区
...Washington and most of the Eastern Seaboard as well.
费用:
The fee:
十亿元
One billion dollars.
十亿元?
A billion dollars.
我欠别人钱
I owe people money.
糟了
Oh, shit.
这是什么地方?
What is this place?
我们要有准备
Here we go.
我不知道 国会亦不知
- I don't know, nor does Congress. - Who's paying for it?
是什么回事?
What the hell is going on?
别说它是个气象站
Don't say this is just a weather station.
显示在屏幕上
Bring the rendering up.
我们把分子光束武器送上轨迹
Recently we deployed a particle-beam weapon into orbit.
说简单一点
In English, please.
需要许多钱 分子光束技技
It's a major cash cow. Particle-beam technology, it's the earthquake deal.
以我所知已终止了那计划
It's my understanding we shut that program down.
我们加以资助
We financed it.
贝克
Breaker, what?
这东西发挥效用了?
This goddamn thing works now?
它效能极好
It works so effectively...
若瞄准罗省地震断层 十五秒后
...that if we targeted the Los Angeles fault lines, in 15 seconds...
亚历桑那会变成滨海地区
...Arizona would be beachfront property.
问题是 别人指挥了卫星
The problem is, someone else is commanding the satellite.
我们无法找到或摧毁它
We couldn't find it or destroy it...
所以我们不可以阻止它
...so we were unable to stop it.
天啊!
Oh, my God!
中国的地震?
China's earthquake?
我们可完全否认
We have full deniability.
糟透!
Shit!
那是典型作风
That's typical.
中情局作风 你知对手是谁吗?
Typical Agency bullshit! Do you know who we're dealing with?
是设计这系统的邓查维
We think it's Travis Dane, the guy who designed the system.
我们的人?
- One of our people? - Not anymore.
他给辞退了 上月他自杀身亡
He was decommissioned. Last month he was an apparent suicide.
他很聪明 能干 但神经病
He's brilliant. He can do anything he puts his mind to, but he's crazy.
你为何雇用狂徒?
Why would you hire a maniac?
因为
Because...
正常的人无法造出这样的武器
...sane people do not build weapons like this.
你认为我们可从中学习
You'd think we'd learn from that.
好吧 把紧急状态提升
All right, we're upgrading to Code 3.
我们快找出那卫星及那杂种吧
Gentlemen, let's find the satellite, and the bastard, now!
没有能量
No power.
掩护和隐藏 你懂得的吧?
Cover and conceal. You know about that, right?
你懂得这样做吧?
You know about that, right?
我们有一客户有私事想求助
One of our customers has a small personal favor to ask.
他想你炸毁一客机
He wants you to blow up an airplane.
告诉他不行 我会炸五角大厦
Tell him to forget about it. I'm going to blow up the Pentagon.
他不加入便无法参与
He either gets on board or gets left behind.
但这人的前妻在这机上
But, sir, the gentleman's ex-wife is on board of this jet.
请转告贝兹上将:
他想你用为地下攻击设计的武器
He wants you to blow up a jet going 500 miles an hour...
炸毁时速五百里的飞机?
...with a weapon designed for subterranean strikes?
他说会额外给我们一亿元
He says he'll pay us an additional $100 million.
真的?
Really?
异频收发器的号码?
Do we have it's transponder numbers?
他现时送来
Sending them now.
我可办到
I can do this.
钱存进我们的帐户他前妻便没命
His ex-wife is history once the money is in our account.
一号会移至位置
Grazer One will be in position in...
他有五分钟
He has five minutes to make the deposit.
里高餐室
线路繁忙
钱已存入苏黎士
The money's hitting Zurich...
对!
...now!
好 开始
Good. Here we go.
牧场一号又回到银幕
Grazer's back on-line.
若他们联上我们便有麻烦
- lf they hooked up, we're in trouble. - Pegasus C Team is in range.
B2轰炸机上有反卫星导弹
We have a B-2 bomber with two anti-satellite missiles on board.
我以为你已截断下面的电源
I thought you cut the power downstairs.
30秒后重发
战机导弹瞄准卫星听候你的命令
Pegasus locked on Grazer One. On your command.
发射
Fire.
我们可成功吗?
Can we get it before it fires?
他们很慢
They are so slow.
为何仍在数? 资料仍在传送
- Why is it counting? - Still getting the feed.
空中地震
Earthquake in midair.
我从没见过这么精彩的
That is the goddamnedest thing I've ever seen.
我们击落了什么?
What the hell did we shoot down?
21秒后重发
若没有击落卫星我们击落什么?
I'll ask you again, if we didn't shoot down Grazer One, what did we shoot?
到下面去看看赫拔
Check on Herb downstairs.
已在传送中删去火车车声
Train noise eliminated from the transmission.
我们准备致电老家吧
Let's get ready to call home.
怎么了?
What's up?
你哪里弄到枪的?
- Where'd you get the gun? - Get anything?
鱼杠 桌球棒 衣服
I got a fishing rod, pool cue and clothes.
你是没用的浑蛋
You're a useless bastard.
这是点四五的枪
Encrypted, no good. This is a.45, okay?
左手 右手 掌心紧压一起
Dynamic tension, left hand, right hand, palms pressed together, okay?
经常要攒前顾后 左看右望
Cover your ass, 12, 3, 6, 9, wherever you look always.
枪指向那里便望那里 明白吗?
Never look in a direction where the gun ain't pointing, understand?
那是谁?
Who the hell is that?
主耶稣
Jesus Christ!
我不是 虽然我从死里复活
Not quite, General Cooper, although I have sort of risen from the dead.
我只是你的老朋友屈维斯 丹
No, it's just your old friend, Travis Dane.
你记得吗?给你辞退的人
You remember? The guy you fired!
我相信你现时在问自己:
And I bet now you're probably asking yourselves:
我们击落了什么?
"What the hell did we just shoot down?"
答案是:
The answer is:
国家安全机构唯一有效的卫星
The NSA's best and only functional real-time down-looking satellite...
NSP一号
... the NSP-1.
你可能查问他们有关卫星的用途
You'll probably be calling them any minute now, asking them for its use.
可惜 由于他们不知它的下落
Unfortunately, since even they don't know where it is...
亦无法帮你们
... they can't help you.
查到他的下落吗?
Have you got him?
快可以了
I'm closing in.
你是知道上次在何处传送
You do know where the last transmission came from.
你就可能查到
You're probably closing in fast...
牧场一号的可能位置
... on Grazer One's probable location.
它就在某一处
It's in there somewhere...
躲在我所创造的50枚假卫星中
... hiding among those 50 ghost satellites I've created...
为你而造的
... just for you.
那捞种死了
Motherfucker's gone.
我的示范证明了
As my demonstration just proved...
游牧者一号是可行的
... Grazer One is viable...
亦能产生效果
... and can produce results.
可再生的效果
Reproducible results.
而为了证明
And to prove it...
我会给你们再示范一次
... I'm going to give you another demonstration of my masterpiece.
45分钟后
In 45 minutes...
牧场一号到了发射的位置时
... as soon as Grazer One is in position for a clear shot...
我会用九成八的威力炸五角大厦
... I'm going to hit the Pentagon with a 98 percent blast.
可摧毁你们说并不存在的反应器
Enough to fracture the nuclear reactor you claim you don't have under there.
你这王八蛋
You son of a bitch.
会有辐射性微尘
We'll have fallout.
会有毁灭
We'll have devastation.
我有事情要办
I've got things to do.
我要你们记着:
I want you to remember:
我在上班前已比你们聪明
I was smarter than all of you before I worked there.
受雇工作时亦比你们聪明
I was smarter than all of you while I worked there.
我仍比你们聪明
And I'm still smarter than all of you.
再见
Au revoir.
他不是从这儿走否则我们会听到
He sure didn't go this way. We would've heard him.
及时追查牧场一号下落的机会如
What are the odds of tracking Grazer down in time?
我们该查询巴黎
We should check over Paris.
试想我们要函盖的范围
Considering the area we must cover...
因此它称为太空
That's why it's called "space."
什么? 大声一点
What's that, son? Speak up.
这个
Well...
我只是说
...I was just saying...
因此它给称为 太空      因为
...that's why they call it "space," because...
有许多的空间
...there's a lot of it.
谢谢
Thank you.
但请静一点
Just be quiet, please.
你去哪儿?
Where are you going?
到火车前面
Front of the train.
找无线电
To look for the radio.
你别现身也别送命
Stay out of sight and don't get killed.
扳开安全制
Safety off...
动力
...dynamic tension...
瞄准 发射
...aim... shoot.
他们没命了
That's their ass now.
你知这是什么吗?海军十字动章
Do you know what this is? This is a Navy Cross.
是英勇作战获勋的
It's awarded for bravery.
这是我爸的 凯西叔叔有两枚
This is my father's. Uncle Casey's got two of them.
他拿的奖章是那么的秘密
He's got medals that are so secret...
他从不给别人看的
...he can never show them to anybody.
他不会让我们有事的
He won't let anything happen to us.
我猜他是个英雄
I guess he's a hero.
这火车不能操作
有入侵者
We have an intruder.
搜查火车
Sweep the train.
搜查
找到入侵者吗?
Found our intruder?
找不到 仍在找
Negative. We're still looking.
你找过?
You clear?
在找
We're checking.
没发现
Nothing.
没有入侵者
We're clear here.
你到处搜查过
Have you checked everywhere?
在车顶搜查
Check on the roof.
什么事?
What?
他在车顶! 在车顶!
On top!
我们受到攻击!
We're under fire!
去捉他
Go get him.
是大个子 他从前列车卡掉下
Got him. He fell off of one of the first cars.
她说他在这儿掉下
She said he fell over here.
这儿有血迹
There's blood here. Here!
她杀了他 他从两卡车中间掉下
She got him. He fell between the first car and the locomotive.
这确定了吗?
Is this a confirmation?
他已给展成肉酱 陈尸路轨了
He's now hamburger. He's probably spread about halfway across the state.
杀了他
We got him.
但他干掉我们六个人
But the bastard took out six men.
你留在这儿 我回去
You stay here, okay? I'm going back.
小心
Be careful.
你说他们训练有素
You said these men were good.
他是谁?
Who was he?
他在下面做什么?
What was he doing downstairs?
那人是个雇拥兵狂徒
The man is a soldier-of-fortune freak.
主办作战营 学员作模拟战争
Ran a war camp in Alabama. They sat around playing paint ball.
事情不是这么简单
That's not the whole story.
沙莫风暴暴露了丹和彭的关系
The relationship between Penn and Dane resurfaced during Desert Storm.
丹死后 我们撤销对他们的监视
When Dane apparently died, we pulled surveillance off them.
这个我们知道
We're aware of that.
两人关系是模糊的
The connection is tenuous.
我告诉你他们有什么关系
Let me tell you what it really is.
另一个中情局没清楚调查的例子
It's another classic example of the CIA not doing their homework.
什么?
Excuse me?
过去数年彭发展出一联繁网
In the last few years, Penn developed a network of contacts.
北韩 美国 尤其在中东
North Korea, here in the US, in particular in the Middle East.
若他和丹结合 他们有资金可用
Best guess is this: If he's hooked up with Dane, they have the money to do it.
他为何要电源?
Why did he need power?
用电话
The phone!
传送成功
通知菲力 告诉他明天上班
Call Philippe, tell him he's working tomorrow.
可恶!
Damn it!
他昨天已上班 找安东尼吧
On second thought, he worked yesterday. Call Antoine.
不 我体内没子弹 你中枪?
No, there's no bullet. No bullet in here.
你以为中枪是这样的吗?
You think this is "been shot"?
才不是呢
This ain't it.
让我看看
Let's see here...
不能使用
Access encoded...
随取记忆体的十亿位元组该可以
Gigabyte of RAM should do the trick.
找到什么?
We are in. What have we got?
电话薄
"Phone book...
食谱
"...recipes.
鸡肉卷
"Chicken cannelloni...
水果沙拉和蜜饯生姜
"...fruit salad with crystallized ginger."
很不错
Sounds good.
我们在哪里
Where are we?
大约在这里
We're about right there.
我们从那儿离开大山约二百里
There, about 200 miles, is where we come out of the mountain.
没电话可用达四小时
We're without phones for four hours?
雷贝克兵法
"Ryback's Tactics."
雷贝克?
Casey-fucking-Ryback?
天啊
Jesus Christ.
雷贝克是谁?
Who's Casey-fucking-Ryback?
是反恐怖份子专家
Casey Ryback's a former SEAL Team Captain, a counter-terrorist expert.
他是我的教官
He was my instructor.
是最好的
He's the best.
我以为你是最好的
I thought you were.
你看见她枪杀的尸体吗?
Did you see the body she shot?
没有 只看见许多血 给火车碾压
No, just a lot of blood. If you get run over by a train...
你看见尸体吗?
Did you see the body?
我假设他死了
I assumed he was dead.
假设是败事之母
Assumption is the mother of fuckups.
各人继续搜索火车
I want every man to resume a full train search...
逐车卡的搜
...inside and out, car by car.
包括空调管剿 间隔车顶 车盘
Including all AC ducting, all paneling, the roof, undercarriage.
不可遗漏!快去!
Absolutely everything! Right now!
我可以的
I can do this.
你看他还活着
You think he's alive?
除非我证实他死了
Until I have confirmation otherwise.
他除杀掉你的人还在车上做什么
What is he doing on my train besides killing your men?
检查乘客名单看是否有人和他同行
Check the manifest. See if he's traveling with anyone.
你说你的百万雇佣兵已足够了
You said your million-dollar mercenaries would be more than enough.
他们是的 打印出来
They are. Print that.
快走!
Move it!
你找错地方张开双腿呆站着
You picked the wrong place to hang out with your legs spread.
我可支持下去的
No, I'm hanging on right here.
雷贝克和一人
Plus one.
可能是女友或孩子
Could be a girlfriend or child.
可能是他妻子
Could be his wife.
妻子是不会说成是 和一人 的
A man doesn't call his wife "plus one."
你要找妞儿吗?
So what? You looking for some babe?
是个饵
Some bait.
这是什么?
What the hell?
这不是货单 这是
This isn't a produce list, this is...
天啊
Oh, my God.
这是谁的血?
Who's fucking blood is this?
回到酒吧车卡 搜查下面的酒吧
Go back to the lounge car. Check the bar downstairs.
怎办?
What are you doing now?
我在制炸弹
What am I doing? I'm making a bomb.
容缩椰子油
他找什么?
What's he looking for?
找我
Me.
你的午餐?
Your lunch?
我何时显身手?
When do I get some action?
我们要拿保护人质的筹码
We're going to take a bargaining chip to protect the hostages.
我要下令疏散总统和高级幕僚
I want an evac order for the President, and senior staff members...
首要任务 并设法别引起恐慌
...on an Alpha status now, and try not to cause a panic.
我看我们没有机会
I don't think we have a chance in hell.
亲爱的 是我
Hi, honey. It's me.
我要你带同吉米今晚离开华府
I want you to take Jamie, and I want you to get out of Washington tonight.
到你母亲家中
Go to your mother's.
是的 还有
Yeah, and...
亲爱的
...honey...
别对别人说
...don't tell anyone.
你叫什么?
What's your name?
柴企 巴比柴企
Zachs. Bobby Zachs.
你不在名单内
You're not on the list.
我是职员
I'm an employee.
你的制服呢?
Where's your uniform?
我免费乘车
I'm deadheading, getting a free ride.
海军十字动章
Navy Cross.
喷雾防身器
Mace.
这个不是
Not Mace...
是胡椒喷剂
...pepper spray.
卖给平民的 一旦习惯了
Sold to civilians. Once you get used to it...
可收通鼻之效
...it just clears the sinuses.
把她带走
Get her and let's go.
放了她
Let her go.
你为何要打火机液体?
Why do you need lighter fluid?
这有如是雷管
It's like a detonator.
好了 包比  进升降机去
Okay, Bobby, get in the elevator.
我要传呼别人
I must go beep someone.
试想像由纽约查斯顿的大火
Imagine a fire from New York to Charleston.
我们可以成功的
We can do this.
你失败了
找人上车顶!
Get a man on the roof!
下两个车卡派两人到下面去
I need two more downstairs in the next two cars!
那混蛋利用空调剿管
The bastard is using the AC ducting!
电脑失灵
Computer's down!
快去行李卡
You and you, get to the baggage car!
抓他!
Get him!
我拿到光谍了
I got the CD.
他在下面 找他
He's downstairs. Go get him.
走
Go.
去
Now.
他们拿走光谍
They have the CD!
那目标光谍
The targeting CD!
没有它我做什么也不行
I can't do anything without it!
走吧
Let's go!
别杀死他
Don't shoot the intruder.
他有光谍
He has the CD.
别走!
Hold it right there!
把光谍给我
Hand over the CD.
他们掉下去
They're off the train.
停车
Stop the train.
退后
Back up.
这火车
This train...
没有光谍便成20吨的废铁
...might as well be 20 tons of scrap metal without that CD.
且慢!
Hold it!
快!
Come on, move!
锡着
Hook up right here.
在这里等
Wait here.
开保险
Safety off...
动力!
...dynamic tension...
没命了
Ass!
是那侍者
It's the porter.
找那侍者!
Check the porter!
你这小浑球
You cocksucker!
他有同党
He's got an accomplice!
是那侍者 我们快抓到他
It's the porter. We're on to him.
别杀他
Don't shoot him.
光谍亦可能在他身上
He could also have the CD.
别向他开枪
Don't put a bullet in it.
把侍者的事告诉我
Tell me about the porter.
光谍
The CD.
交出来
Hand it over.
在下面
Down there.
他在火车下哪一处?
Where did he go under the train?
前面两车卡
Two cars up.
你们不识相
You pricks never learn.
别动!
Freeze!
举手!
Get your damn hands up.
把手举高!
Up where I can see them!
光谍在哪?
Where's the CD?
口袋撕破了 它丢了
I ripped my pocket. It fell out.
快拿光谍出来
Don't bullshit with me. Show me that CD...
否则我杀了你
...or I'll cap your black ass, bitch!
把口袋翻出
Empty your pockets.
快点!
Right now!
好吧
All right, man!
我只是个年轻人 我想对你说
I'm just a kid. I'm just a kid, I'm trying to tell you.
我丢失了
- Do it! - I lost it there.
什么也丢了
I ripped my pocket. Everything fell out.
我可杀了你
Only thing I've got is your ass!
查过侍者了
Porter checked.
有志者事竟成
"Chance favors the prepared mind."
糟了
Oh, shit.
往西走 全速开行
Take us west. Full ahead.
糟了
Oh, shit.
你叔叔不是我所想的那么好
Your uncle wasn't as good as I thought.
你已同步了 继续吧
You're back on-line. Now, get on with it.
我们没失去重要仪器 仍可继续
We haven't lost anything vital. I have enough to do this.
休斯顿 现时是二十分钟
Houston, Tranquility Base here. We are now at T minus 20 minutes...
而且
...and...
在倒数
...counting.
那浑蛋开始倒数了
That bastard started the countdown.
威廉
Williams.
二十分钟后删除不能令卫星射向 华府的轨迹
Eliminate orbits that don't offer Grazer a shot at Washington in 20 minutes.
我们要删除全部
We must eliminate all of them.
但只剩一枚导弹
- We only have one Pegasus left. - We don't need one.
最后一个瞄准卫星采自毁程式
On the last one we lock on the satellite and use the self-destruct.
定要成事
Make it happen.
开始消灭卫星
Start knocking them off.
我们已删去22个可能性
- We've eliminated 22 possibilities. - Excellent.
23个
Twenty-three.
厨师有口信给你
A cook has a message.
他说他有三号密码口信
He says he has a Code 3 message.
把他转驳到扬声器
Patch him through on the audio.
贝兹在吗?
Is Joint Chief of Staff Bates there, please?
我是贝兹上将
This is Admiral Bates speaking.
我有传真讯息给你
Sir, I have a fax message for you.
写着:
It reads:
上将 一伙武装人员
"Admiral, a force of armed men...
人数可能在20名以上
"...probably numbering above 20...
已胁持了由丹佛往麻省的
"...has taken over the Grand Continental passenger train...
大陆火车客车
"...traveling from Denver to LA.
主要电磁射线仪器
"Key signature equipment of...
卫星传送仪器已装置在车上
"...high-bandwidth satellite transmission equipment has been loaded on board. "
是丹麦人! 攻击者似乎很专业
- It's Dane! - "Aggressors appear to be professionals...
并且全副武装    查出那列车的正确地点
- "...and fully armed." - Get me the exact location of that train.
是谁发出这讯息的
Who sent the message?
雷贝克
Casey Ryback.
雷贝克在这列车上?
Casey Ryback? Casey Ryback's on this train?
他做什么?
What is he doing?
交给凯西好了
Leave it to Casey.
和他的侄女渡假
On vacation with his niece, sir.
最接近的空军攻击部队
What's the closest air-strike group?
飞机展览的隐形轰炸机
Stealth, sir, from the air show.
立即命它们起飞
Get them armed and on their way.
车上有二百多名乘客
There's over 200 people on that train.
华盛顿有八百多万人
There are over eight million people in Washington.
除非赖能在18分内有奇迹出现
Unless Ryback performs a miracle in 18 minutes, I have no choice.
派隐形战机
Scramble the Stealths.
我很失望
I'm disappointed.
我很想和凯西单打独斗
I looked forward to going head-to-head with the great Casey...
很出色
Man, that was good.
是他教你的吗?
Did he teach you that?
可惜
Pity...
你会是很好的战士
...you could have been very, very good.
别惹她
She's insurance, leave her alone.
雷贝克死了
Ryback's gone, Dane.
你看见尸体吗?
Did you see the body?
假设是败事之母
"Assumption is the mother of all fuckups."
没关系 反正她会死
It doesn't matter, she'll die anyway...
和其他乘客一起
...with all the rest.
雷贝克可能死了 可能活着
Ryback may be dead, he may be alive...
但他并不在列车上
...but he is not on this train.
我不该回到车上的
I shouldn't have got back on this train.
扔下枪
Drop the gun.
扔下
Drop it!
我从不认为自己邪恶
I never considered myself vicious...
但你
...but you...
你像是蟑螂
...you're like a cockroach!
蟑螂出现时你会怎办?
So what do you do when the bastard shows himself?
你捏死它 对吗?
You squash him, right?
你明白我的意思吗?杂工?
You get what I'm saying here, busboy?
我是侍者
I'm a porter...
不是杂工
...not a busboy.
侍者先生
Okay, Mr. Porter...
你有种
...you got balls, man.
所以我让你决定
So I'm going to let you decide.
你想正面死去
You want to see it coming...
还是背向着受死?
...or to turn around?
你
Say...
要救我吗?
...want to help me?
你真不好惹
You're a bad motherfucker.
但我们去杀敌吧
Let's go kick some more ass, though.
好极
Cool, man.
恭喜 各位
Congratulations, gentlemen...
现时有十亿元
...there is now one billion dollars...
在瑞士等着我们去拿
...waiting for us in the land of banks, cheese and cuckoo clocks.
我们现在要做的
All we must do now...
是把华府炸了
... is blow up Washington, DC.
他说的是那场火
That'd be the fire.
下一站会有人接你们
You will be picked up at the next stop.
多谢你们参加
Thank you for your participation.
我说的不算错
It is sort of true.
你们在另一空间行进
You're traveling in another dimension...
不是视与听的 而是意志的
...not only of sight and sound, but of mind.
前面有一路标 你们的下一站
There's a signpost up ahead. Your next stop:
无讯号
Dark territory.
谁说我的想法呆扳
Who says I have a one-track mind?
火车在错误的一方
The town's on the wrong side.
我们入错了路轨
We're not on the right tracks.
我们由内面驶过  不是由外面
We always pass it on the inside, not the outside.
我们去哪里
Where are they taking us?
8时内华达巡逻快车驶过
8:00, Nevada Petrol Express.
会相撞 若不想办法便会没命
We're going to collide. If we don't do something, we'll die.
那列车很大
This is a big motherfucker.
前面有六卡机车 长约一里
It has six locos up front, about a mile long...
载有八十万加仑汽油
...and has 800,000 gallons of gasoline.
你不会让他们得程吧?
You won't let them get away with it.
不 我会施展浑身解数
No, I'm going to get my bag of tricks...
我们会拯救那些人质
...and we are going to rescue these hostages.
撞车警报
那是内华达快车
That's the Nevada Petrol Express.
载有八十万加仑的汽油
It's carrying 800,000 gallons of gasoline.
无法联络他们吗?
Can't we contact them?
在无讯号地区便不能
Not while they're in dark territory. There is no reception in the canyons.
何时会相撞?能摧毁仪器吗?
When will they hit? Will it do the job?
会很接近但我看不会
It's going to be close, but... I don't think so.
快完成了但仍剩下十一个可能性
We're closing in, sir, but there are 11 possibles left.
可及时消除它们吗?
Can you eliminate them in time?
不行
No, sir.
狐步战机 向目标飞去
Foxtrot Flight, vectoring in on target.
准许轰炸机执行任务
Green light the bombers.
知道 狐步飞向目标
Roger. Foxtrot heading zero.
主原谅我们
God forgive us.
雷达有动静
Something's coming in.
断续的讯号 很微弱
Intermittent signal, very faint.
F一117战机
F-117s.
是隐形战机
Stealths.
他们发现我们了
They found us.
可恶的雷贝克
Casey-fucking-Ryback.
击落它们
Shoot them down.
我要解除瞄准华府
I'd have to unlock Grazer from Washington.
没有异频雷达收发号码不能瞄准
I don't have the transponder numbers. I can't target them!
他们会杀死所有人质
They'd kill all the hostages.
颤动
Turbulence.
若它移动 卫星可测到
If it moves, Grazer can see it.
他们飞过时会触动空气
They disturb the air as they fly through it.
低高度的颤动  便可以追测得到
Low-altitude turbulence, that's how you find these things.
你在那儿
There you are...
隐形战机
...Stealths.
我可瞄准它们
I can target these.
小姐!
Lady!
你为何还不出来
What's taking you so long?
两分钟已到了
You've had your two minutes.
我们是好人
We're the good guys.
慢着 你去哪里?
Wait a minute. Where are you going?
它们分开了
- They split up. - Is that a problem?
它飞过前我无法令卫星对准华府
I won't get Grazer onto DC before it passes.
快出来
Come out now.
我的胸罩断了
I broke my bra.
难过美人关
Tits to die for, huh?
人质在哪儿?
Where are the hostages?
上层 去!
They're upstairs! Go!
先击落你
You first.
道别吧
Say good night, Gracie.
击落了
Got you.
赖攻入人质车卡
Ryback's hitting the hostage cars.
好一个雷贝克!
Good old Ryback!
狐步二号 已瞄准目标
ATAC, Foxtrot Two. Target is locked on. I have tone.
我真行
Damn, I'm good.
天啊
Jesus.
替我接总统
Get me the President.
我要去救我侄女了
I'm coming to get my niece now.
来救她吧
Come and get her.
你能应付吗?
Why are you bringing Ryback here? Can you handle this?
看来你失败了 立即走吧
It looks like you fucked up. It's time to cut and run.
什么?
Excuse me?
还有谁认为我失败?
Anyone else think I fucked up?
列车分开了
The cars are separating!
你做什么?
What are you doing?
我来帮你
Coming to help you.
你现在是英雄了?
You're a hero now?
你是英雄
You're the hero.
我们自由了!
We're free!
你想帮忙便爬上直升机指挥机师
You want to help? Climb up that ladder and commandeer that helo.
你疯了吗?爬上去?
Are you crazy? Climb up there?
可能会失败 但试试看
It might not work, but try.
你去哪儿?
Where are you going?
那女孩
The girl.
宁静 这是麻雀
Tranquility, this is Sparrow. I'm in position. Over.
这是宁静 照计划保持原位
This is Tranquility. Hold position as planned. Out.
把梯子移近一点
Hey, bring that ladder closer.
你看不见我想做英雄吗?
Can't you see I'm trying to be a hero?
这样才是
That's better.
这是麻雀 已接了第一个人
This is Sparrow. We made our first pickup.
你没有 快上去应付吧
The hell you have. Get up there and deal with that.
什么回事?
What's going on?
揍他吧!
Kick his butt!
我们教他怎样飞
Honey, we sure taught that boy how to fly.
是的
We sure did.
现在把直升机停留在这儿
Now we're going to keep this chopper right here.
否则便杀了你 你明白吗?
Or I'm going to blow your brains out! You got that, honey?
让我杀了雷贝克
Let me handle Ryback.
你应付技技方面的事
You take care of the techno shit.
他是我的
He's mine.
我亲手杀了他
I'll take him myself, hand to hand.
我的假卫星你们要掩掩我的宝贝
Come on my little ghost satellites, I need you with me to hide my baby...
好让它把华府炸个稀烂
...so she can blow the fuck out of Washington.
你去送死吧
Go get your throat ripped out.
我要杀八百万人和去拿十亿元
I got eight million people to kill, and one billion dollars to pick up.
谢谢
Thank you, sir.
总统等人已疏散了
The President and staff have been evacuated.
若不能阻止会有百万计的人死亡
Leaving millions of innocent people to die if we don't stop it.
现在要用科学卫星了
We must use Pegasus now.
但是
But, sir...
仍有八个可能性
...we still have eight possibilities.
选一个吧
Pick one.
快!
Now!
K吧
Kappa.
谢谢 目标是K 准备发射
Thank you. Kappa's the target. Stand by and launch.
我从不害怕任何人
I've never been afraid of anybody.
但你的叔叔使我害怕
But that uncle of yours scares me.
我喜欢
And I like it.
你和我打 否则我和她同归于尽
It's you and me... or me and her.
你要抓紧否则粉身碎骨
Now, you hold on real tight and you'll stay in one piece.
你弄破我的外衣
Fuck, you ruined my coat.
早安
Good morning.
起来
从没有人在厨房能胜过我
Nobody beats me in the kitchen.
我走了 我不需要这些 我要的
I must go. Won't need any of this anymore. Everything I need...
在这儿
...is right here.
快车随时驶至
The Petrol Express will be here in a minute.
好好享受生命
Have a nice life.
你的余生
What's left of it.
你再走近我便扔下手榴弹
You take one step and I'm dropping this grenade.
扔吧
Drop it.
没命中
Pegasus missed.
不是K
It wasn't Kappa.
天啊
Jesus.
杀我不会有好处
Shooting me won't do any good.
他们无法破我的假卫星
ATAC can't get past my ghost satellites.
亦无法破我的密码程式
And you can't get past my encrypted program.
你是说我无法把它关掉吗?
You mean to tell me there's no way I can shut that off?
没办法
No way.
恢复控制游牧者一号
我倒没想过
I never thought of that.
是D
It was Delta.
瞄准了
We're locked on.
击中!
Hit it!
稳定梯子 把直升机停在这儿
Hold the ladder. And keep this chopper right here.
我从没怀疑你
I never doubted you.
你有的
Oh, yes, you did.
这是很动人的时刻
This is a real sweet Hallmark moment, but...
但我们可以回家去了吗 凯西叔
...can we go home now, Uncle Casey?
这是505NM直升机
This is Helo 505 November-Mike.
有讯息 我转过来
Sir, there's a message coming in. I'll patch it through.
我是雷贝克
This is Casey Ryback.
人质安全
The hostages are safe.